这是我们谈下绩效标准的筹码
It's there for leverage so that we can lock down performance standards.
你不能随便拿集体谈判当筹码
You don't toss around their right to collective bargaining like a poker chip.
我们不这么做  他们就不让步
If we don't, they won't budge.
马蒂・斯比奈拉看过了吗
Has Marty Spinella seen this?
给他看的跟这不一样
Not the version I showed him.
这么说你对他撒谎了
So you lied to his face.
不  我改变了我承诺的内容
No. I revised the parameters of my promise.
也就是撒谎
Which is lying.
是政治
Which is politics...
是你精通之道  鲍勃
the sort you're well versed in, Bob.
我来和你谈谈政治
Here's some politics for you.
我允许这个法案辩论投票
I allow this to go to the floor,
下次选举我会死无葬身之地
I get murdered next election.
这是总统的意思
This is coming from the President.
据我所知
Last time I checked,
我还是民主党人  弗兰克
I was still a Democrat, Frank,
你也是
and you were too.
你想告诉我总统不是了吗
Are you telling me the President isn't?
因为他现在表现得像个十足的共和党人
Because he's acting a hell of a lot like a Republican.
鲍勃不是我们这边的吗
I thought Bob was on our team.
让他和总统坐下来谈十分钟
Just sit him down with the President ten minutes.
集体谈判的条款不能改
We won't touch collective bargaining.
你想听我对此的意见吗
Are you interested in my advice on this,
还是只想让我传个话
or do you just want me to deliver the message?
我永远想听你的意见  弗兰克
I'm always interested in your advice, Frank.
博奇是对的  你这样会激怒很多人
Birch is right. You're going to burn a lot of bridges.
总统至少应该坐下和他谈谈
The President should at least sit down with him
让他说说他的看法
and let him make his case.
你跟鲍勃说
You tell Bob
只要他肯让法案进入辩论投票
I'm happy to schedule a meeting with the President
我就给他安排和总统的见面
once he's set a date to put this bill on the floor.
总统可以一边玩去了
The President can fuck himself.
这是党章  是他竞选的核心理念
This is the platform. It's what he ran on.
我才不在乎他的理念是什么
I don't give a shit what he ran on.
他休想压倒议会
He can't steamroll the house.
不要忘记
And don't forget,
你是为我工作  弗兰克  不是为他
you work for me, Frank, not him.
他想让法案辩论投票
If he wants something on the floor,
就必须直接来找我说
he's gonna have to talk to me directly.
我知道你很为你的家伙骄傲  鲍勃
I know you take a lot of pride in your manhood, Bob,
的确令人刮目相看
and it's impressive,
但不管你多大
but as big as it is,
琳达还是会让你吃闭门羹
Linda can still shut the door on it.
告诉瓦斯奎兹法案没戏
Tell Vasquez the bill is dead.
他不是头一次跟我来这套了
That's not the first time he's pulled that stunt on me.
也许我不该说什么
Probably should have held my tongue,
但我就是忍不住想看他萎下去的样子
but I just couldn't resist the chance to see him shrivel.
早上好
Good morning.
弗兰克
Frank.
总统先生
Mr. President.
琳达
Linda.
我们把法案中的反集体谈判条款去掉
Let's strike the anti-collective bargaining provision from the bill.
琳达和我谈过了  我认为她的观点很正确
Linda and I have talked it over, and I think she's right on this.
告诉鲍勃他可以明天下午过来
Tell Bob he can come by tomorrow afternoon.
先生  恕我冒犯
Sir, respectfully,
我认为你不该满足他的愿望
I do not think you should give him the satisfaction.
那是为什么
Well, give me a reason.
会让我们显得软弱
Makes us appear weak.
这是一个建立您权威的好机会
There's an opportunity for you to establish your supremacy.
我们应该抓住这个机会
We should seize it.
但博奇如果不合作
But without Birch's cooperation,
法案还没开始辩论投票我们就会举步维艰
we're fighting an uphill battle before we even get the bill to the floor.
弗兰克  这个我们谈过了
Frank, we discussed this.
先生  如果你现在放弃
Sir, if you give in now,
博奇在接下来的四年里
Birch will walk all over you
就会对你为所欲为
for the next four years.
我能让法案不做删减地进入辩论
I can get this bill on the house floor as is.
我保证
I promise you.
好吧  弗兰克  给我露一手吧
All right, Frank. Show me what you can do.
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
她刚刚想窃取我的主意
That was her trying to take credit for my idea.
还是她不肯接受的建议  不可忍受
Advice she wouldn't take from me... unacceptable.
我决不允许她卖我的东西
I will not allow her to sell my goods
还不给我好处
when she cuts me out of the profits.
我明确说过不许接受采访
I specifically told her no interviews.
她违抗我的命令
She disobeyed me...
不止一次
not just once.
上个月就至少有8次
At least eight times in the past month.
她不能走  汤姆
She stays, Tom.
她不尊重我的权威  玛格丽特
She has no respect for my authority, Margaret.
我说了  她不能走
I said she stays.
我们有规则
There are rules.
做事有准则
There's a way of doing things.
如果我的记者不听...
If I have a reporter who won't listen to...
两个大一女生一起搬进她们的宿舍
two freshmen girls are moving into their dorm room together.
一个来自佐治亚州
One of them's from Georgia,
另一个来自康涅狄格州
one of them's from Connecticut.
康涅狄格的女孩在帮她妈妈挂窗帘
The girl from Connecticut's helping her mother put up curtains.
佐治亚的姑娘对她们说
The girl from Georgia turns to them and says,
你们好啊  你们打哪来
"Hi. Where y'all from?"
康涅狄格州姑娘说
The girl from Connecticut says,
我们来自一个
"We're from a place where we know
句子不以介词结尾的地方
not to end a sentence with a preposition."
佐治亚的姑娘说  不好意思
The girl from Georgia says, "Oh, beg my pardon.
你们打哪来
Where y'all from...
婊子
cunt?"
以前听过吗
You heard that one before?
听过其他版本  没那么粗鲁
A version of it. With softer language.
汤姆  我们不需要循规蹈矩的人
Tom, we don't need people who follow the rules.
我们需要有个性的人
We need people with personality.
我们需要佐伊这张面孔  她的能量
We want Zoe's face, her energy.
要尽可能让她多上电视
We want to get her on TV as much as possible.
这能让我们脱颖而出
It helps us cut through the noise.
明白吗
See what I'm saying?
明白了  玛格丽特
I hear you, Margaret.
谢谢  汤姆
Thank you, Tom.
谢谢你了
Thank you.
请进
Come in.
我以为
Oh. I, uh, thought...
我本想跟伊芙琳打个招呼
I wanted to say hi to Evelyn.
伊芙琳
Evelyn?
这原来是她的办公室
This was her office.
我想她已经不在这儿工作了
I don't think she works here anymore.
吉莉安・科尔
Gillian Cole.
我几周前刚加入的
I came on board a couple of weeks ago.
世界之井的吉莉安吗
Gillian. World well.
是啊
Yeah.
我听过你不少好事
I've heard great things.
雷米・丹顿
Remy Danton.
你是克莱尔的同事吗
You work with Claire?
算是吧
In a way.
你好  雷米
Hello, Remy.
克莱尔
Claire.
-看来你见过吉莉安了  -是啊  刚刚认识
- I see you've met Gillian.   - Yes, just now.
她在为我们做了不起的工作
She's doing fantastic work for us,
如你所见
as you can see.
红色是已完工的水井
Red is completed wells,
绿色是可能地点
green, uh, potential sites,
黄色是获得许可的
yellow approved sites,
蓝色是过滤中心
and blue are the filtration centers.
很好  你喜欢这里吗
Nice. So you liking it here?
喜欢啊  我和工作人员都喜欢
Yeah. My staff and I are loving it.
克莱尔为我们创造了许多机会
Claire's opened a lot of doors for us.
克莱尔就是这样
Sounds like Claire.
去我办公室吧
Shall we head to my office?
吉莉安  很高兴认识你
Gillian, nice to meet you.
我也是
Nice to meet you.
怎么回事
What happened?
事情变复杂了
Things got complicated.
桑科当时面临困境
San Corp was in a difficult situation.
我以为遇到困难
I would have thought you'd step up
你会出面解决
when things were difficult,
而不是拿捐款作交换条件
not hold the donation hostage.
但现在又没那么复杂了
Well, things are less complicated now.
他们又愿意捐款了
The donation is back on the table.
我被迫炒了半数员工
I had to fire half my staff.
你可以再把他们雇回来了
Now you can hire them back.
桑科愿将最初承诺金额翻倍
San Corp is prepared to double its initial commitment...
本季度一次性支付150万
1.5 million, lump sum, this quarter.
-为什么  -和之前一样  公关
- Why? - Public relations. Same as before.
他们想从弗兰西斯那里得到什么
And what do they want from Francis?
我们跟弗兰克都扯平了
Things are square with Frank.
我们只谈净水计划的事
We're only talking about the C.W.I.
但为什么要翻倍
But why double it?
因为我说服了他们
Because I said they should.
他们给的越多  你们能做的也越多
The more they give, the more you can do.
你们做的越多  他们就越有面子
The more you can do, the better they look.
他们雇格兰顿-希尔
And that's why they hired Glendon Hill...
就是为了撑门面
to make them look good.
他们还雇你在国会拉拢人
And they also hired you to get traction in congress.
这次不同
Not in this case.
我们想建立长期合作关系  克莱尔
We want a long-term partnership, Claire.
这是对未来的投资
This is an investment in the future.
我们没有其他要求
We're not attaching strings.
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
他们希望能尽快落实
They'd really love to move quickly on this.
我说了我会考虑的
I said I'll think about it.
玛德琳  你得把这个发过来
Madeleine, you have to email me this shit.
我需要书面文件
I need it in writing.
而且还有一个多小时呢
And with more than an hour's notice.
是啊  我知道
Yeah, I know that,
但你得理解  我们有计划的
but you have to understand we... we have a plan.
我们做事有自己的方法
We have a way that we do this,
如果你...
and when you...
好吧
Okay.
好
Fine.
嗯  再见
Yeah. Yeah. Bye.
玛德琳临时起意
Madeleine has decided to have
要跟她在交友网上认识的男友
a spur-of-the-moment trip to Orlando with her
去奥兰多旅行
latest eHarmony catch.
不事先通知  都不说一声
No heads-up, no warning.
孩子们呢
The kids?
他们两点半放学
They get out of school at 2:30.
我可以去和船厂的人会面
I can do the shipbuilders meeting.
真的
You sure?
是的  只是个公共事务小组而已
Yeah, it's just a public affairs team.
回头我向你报告  你明天再打给他们
I'll brief you, and then you can call them tomorrow.
你去接孩子吧
Go get your kids.
雷米今天早上去过我办公室
Remy came by this morning. To the office.
他想干什么
What does he want?
捐款的事又有门了
The donation's back on the table.
数额翻了一番  有150万
They've doubled it to 1.5 million.
-你回绝了吧  -没有
- You said no, right? - I didn't.
他并不图你任何回报  弗兰西斯
He doesn't want anything from you, Francis.
得了吧  克莱尔  你这还不懂吗
Come on, Claire. You know better than that.
我特意问过的
I specifically asked.
也许他现在不求回报
Maybe not right now,
他是我一手提拔的
but look, I invented this guy, all right?
迈出这一步就刹不住了
It's a slippery slope. You...
想想有了这笔钱我能做多少事
Think of what I can do with this money.
我能把辞退的职员全部请回来
I can hire back the people I let go.
还能加快吉莉安那些项目的
I can help accelerate the funding for the projects
融资进度
that Gillian has brought in.
资金的事我们可以另想办法
Let's find another way to raise the money.
但这笔钱唾手可得
But it's right there at my feet.
克莱尔  我现在已经百事缠身了
Claire, I have too much on my plate right now.
不能再被桑科公司纠缠上
I can't have San corp breathing down my neck again.
我不能让雷米
I can't have Remy...
那是雷米啊
Look, it is Remy.
他太了解我了  这很危险
He knows me too well. It's dangerous.
要顾全大局
Look at the bigger picture here.
我恳求你
I'm asking.
你这不是恳求
No. You're not.
克莱尔
Claire.
我会用回复他的话答复你
I'll tell you what I told him.
你说
Which was?
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
我知道最近我们有些紧张
I know there's been some tension,
而且我应该负主要责任
and I'm probably more to blame than you are.
但过去的事就让它过去吧
But I'd like to put that behind us.
佐伊
Zoe,
你将成为我们新一任驻白宫记者
you're going to be our new White House correspondent.
那简宁呢
What about Janine?
升任中西部总编辑
I promoted her to Midwest Bureau chief.
她同意了吗
She's okay with that?
她舍得放弃白宫的工作
She wants to give up the White House?
这是我的决定
It's the decision I've made.
可简宁毕竟经验丰富
It's just that Janine has so much experience.
我还以为你会很兴奋呢
I thought you'd be more excited about this.
抱歉  我还以为你叫我进来是要
I'm sorry. I... I just thought you brought me in here to...
我不知道
I don't know.
解雇你
To fire you.
也许吧
Maybe.
都过去了
Water under the bridge.
我们要重新开始
We're starting over.
那么  你准备好了吗
So are you ready to take this on?
我能考虑一下吗
Can I think about it?
有一份白宫的工作摆在面前
People usually don't have to think about it
人们一般不用考虑的  佐伊
when they're offered the White House, Zoe.
只要一两天就好
Just a day or two.
简宁将乘周五的航班飞往芝加哥
Janine is booked for a flight to Chicago on Friday.
我会在那之前回复你
I'll let you know before then.
我只是要
I just need to...
谢谢你  汤姆
Thank you. Thank you, Tom.
大卫・拉斯姆森是多数党领袖
David Rasmussen is the majority leader,
也就是说他的职位在我之上
which means he's one step above me
在博奇之下
and one below Birch,
就像夹在一匹饿极的狼
which is akin to being between a very hungry wolf
和一只好斗的羊之间
and a very quarrelsome sheep.
羊群或是狼群  看看他会选择哪一边
Let's see if he stays with the herd or joins the pack.
大卫  不介意我坐这儿吧
David. You mind if I join you?
请坐  就吃沙拉啊
Please. A salad, huh?
是啊  我想好好照顾自己
Yes. I'm trying to take better care of myself.
不错嘛  节食吗
Good man. Diet?
节食  锻炼  各种方法
Diet, exercise, everything.
你也该照顾好自己
You ought to take better care of yourself too.
他们这儿的披萨实在太美味了
Well, they should stop serving such good pizza.
我不是指饮食
Oh, I'm not talking about the food.
我是指博奇
I'm talking about Birch.
你要想当上议长
You are never going to be speaker
就必须得有所行动
unless you do something about it.
我对自己的位置很满意
I'm very satisfied where I am.
-拜托  -就目前来说  确实满意
- Oh, come on. - For the time being, yeah.
一时就是永远
Time being never.
你想成为议长
The only way you become Speaker
只有可能是博奇落选或退休
is if Birch loses his district or retires,
在你我老到要装假牙之前
neither of which is going to happen
这两种情况都不会发生
before you and I have dentures.
我不喜欢你这番话的势头  弗兰克
I'm not happy where this conversation is going, Frank.
你想做议长  我知道你想
If you want it, and I know you do,
我有个办法
there's a way.
好了  我不能...
Okay. Right. I can't...
票数过半就可以  也就是218票
all you need is a simple majority... 218 votes.
我们在共和党能得到205票
We're going to get at least 205 out of the G.O.P.,
这样  再有民主党13票就行
and after that, all you need is 13 Democrats.
你我手里就有两票
You and I make two.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
稍稍考虑一下吧
Just consider it for a moment.
你想和共和党串通
You want to collude with the Republicans?
我不想
I don't want to,
但如果能让你当上议长  我会的
but I would if you become Speaker in the process.
这种事没有先例
Never been done before.
凡事都有第一次
There's a first time for everything.
这太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
共和党会很乐意杀杀鲍勃的威风
The Republicans would love a chance to knock Bob down a peg or two.
而你想帮他们
And you want to help them.
我想帮我们
I want to help us.
鲍勃不会和白宫合作
Bob will not play ball with the White House.
你是个通情达理的人  大卫  他不是
Now, you're a reasonable man, David, and he's not.
你知道我是什么人吗
You know what I am?
我是个谨慎的人
I'm a discreet man.
所以算你走运
You're lucky for that.
我不会跟鲍勃说今天的事
I'm not going to mention this to Bob,
你要是再提
but if you ever bring it up again,
我就没办法了
I won't have a choice.
看来他选择了羊群
Looks like he opted for the herd.
克莱尔
Claire.
我想为南苏丹项目的
I'd like to put an order for the water filters
滤水器和钻井机械下订单
and the well-digging equipment for the South Sudan project.
我们能讨论一下预算问题吗
Can we talk about the budget?
-需要多少  -20万
- How much? - 200,000.
一个项目就要这么多
For one project?
我知道很多
I know it's a lot,
但这是我们在非洲的旗舰项目
but it'll be our flagship project in Africa,
我们也是那里首家
and we would be the first organization there
有如此规模的机构
to work on this scale.
我想先核对一下详情
I'd like to go over the specifics first.
我已经做好了预算表
I have the budget right here.
我先查一下留言  就去找你
Let me just grab my messages, and then I'll come in to you.
好  我在办公室等你
Okay. I'll be in my office.
我不在时有电话打来吗
Any calls while I was out?
都放你桌上了  这个是快递送来的
They're on the desk, and this came by messenger.
克莱尔  你不需要桑科  你有我呢  弗兰克
亚当  我是克莱尔
Adam. It's Claire.
对  我知道  是这样
Yes. I know. It has.
没事  只是想你了
No reason. I was just thinking about you.
你说得对  是谎话
You're right. It is a lie.
我确实有事
I do have a reason.
我需要你
I need to use you.
白宫就是新闻死掉的地方
The White House is where news goes to die.
净是些陈词滥调
Everything's canned.
那些精心编排的讲话...
These perfectly prepared statements...
那是份威风的工作  佐伊
it's a prestigious job, Zoe.
我九年级的时候是这样的
Used to be, when I was in ninth grade.
现在就是块墓地
Now it's a graveyard.
现在唯一还算有意思的事
The only halfway interesting thing they do
就是每年一度的晚宴
is throw a big dinner party once a year
他们不是自我吹捧
where they pat themselves on the back
就是跟明星勾肩搭背
and rub shoulders with movie stars.
谁要看那个
Who needs that?
从你到这里开始
Every day since you started here,
每天都在求我给你升职  而现在...
you've begged me to move you up, and now...
我的人生理想
My goal in life is not
不是在《先驱报》一步步爬到
to climb up the Herald's ladder one rung at a time
我能有自己的文具
until I've got my own stationery.
我们有些人很珍惜在这样一家报社的发展
Some of us value a career at a paper like this.
抱歉  我不是那个意思...
I'm sorry. I didn't mean for that to come off...
但就是这个感觉  而且你已经跳级了
Well, it did, and you skipped a few rungs, by the way.
想怎么做随便你  佐伊
Do what you want to do, Zoe,
但你要是希望我能给你鼓劲
but if you want me to be your cheerleader and say,
说"推掉它"  我做不到
"Yeah, turn it down," I won't.
我刚来这里时  会为那份工作拼命
I would have killed for that job when I first started here.
113届国会  美国众议院
把菲柯特放在"倾向赞成"里
Put Fichtner in the "Leaning yes" Column.
你不觉得他是中立的吗
Don't you think he's a neutral?
他讨厌博奇
He hates Birch.
是  但他能在财政委员会任职还靠博奇
Yeah, but he owes Birch for the ways and means appointment.
把他放在"中立"里  还有谁
Put him in "Neutral." Who else?
众议院投票计数
雷米兹是中立的吗
Ramirez is a neutral?
这个表格太不可靠了
Oh, this list is so shaky.
他们要是有谁跟鲍勃通了气...
Any one of them leaks it to Bob...
不  我们只需要一个人
No, what we need is one name,
一个能说动12个人的人
one person who can deliver 12.
黑人党团
The black caucus.
乌麦克
Womack.
我们给他什么好处
What can we offer him?
他需要什么
What does he need?
我去调他的档案
Let me pull up his file.
赞成
有了
Here we go.
他选区的麦喀顿空军基地雇了三千人
McCudden air force base employs 3,000 people in his district.
基地今年可能被国防部关掉
It's on the D.O.D.'s chopping block this year.
军事基地整合委员会里有熟人吗
Who do we know on the BRAC commission?
这很危险
That's dangerous.
摆布国防部或军事基地整合委员会
The trail leads back to us trying to influence
会被人查到的
the D.O.D. or the BRAC.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
我们只要关掉另一个基地
What we do is we close another base.
给国防部留出足够的预算
We leave enough money in the D.O.D.'s budget
让乌麦克的基地逃过一劫
to keep Womack's base off the list.
我们需要的是
What we need...
一个听命于我们的人
Is someone we own.
彼得・罗素
爸爸  我饿了
Dad, I'm hungry.
来了  宝贝
Coming, buddy.
来啦
Here we go.
这份有芝士
With cheese.
这份没有芝士
Without cheese.
爸爸
Um, dad?
怎么了
Yeah.
看着真恶心
That looks pretty disgusting.
看起来的确挺恶心
Yeah, it looks disgusting.
外表不重要  味道才是关键
It's not how it looks, it's how it tastes.
再来把叉子就好了
And a fork would be nice.
该死  好的  稍等
Shit. Okay. Hold on.
你好
Hello.
晚上好  罗素先生
Good evening, Mr. Russo.
有位安德伍德先生来访
There's a Mr. Underwood here to see you.
好的  请他上来
Uh... Okay. Send him up.
你们好啊
Hi, there.
这是凯文  这是萨拉
This is Kevin, this is Sara.
我是弗兰克  很高兴见到二位
Hi. I'm Frank. Nice to meet you both.
-你是爸爸的同事吗  -是的
- Do you work with dad? - I do.
安德伍德议员是爸爸的老板
Congressman Underwood is daddy's boss.
我还以为你没有老板
I thought you didn't have a boss.
人人都有老板  甜心
Everybody has a boss, sweetheart,
议员也不例外
even congressmen.
把晚餐拿去卧室里吃吧
Why don't you take your dinner and go into the bedroom?
-可我想看电视  -现在就去
- But I wanted to watch TV. - Go now.
孩子们很可爱
Cute kids.
是啊  我爱他们
Yeah, I like them.
来杯喝的怎么样
Can I get you a drink?
不用  我很快就走
No, I won't be here long.
好的  请坐
Yeah. Have a seat.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
那是索尼次时代掌机吗
Is that a ps vita?
都有什么游戏
Which games does he have?
一应俱全
All of them.
我家有个游戏机
I have a console at home.
我常用来放松
I play sometimes to relax.
我该买台这个放车上
I ought to get one of these for the car.
彼得
So, Peter,
我们得关掉你选区的造船厂
we need to close the shipyard in your district.
明天军事基地整合委员会听证会
The BRAC hearing is tomorrow.
你不要努力争取
You won't put up your usual fight.
也不要提供任何证词
You have zero testimony to add.
我不能这么做
I can't do that.
你能的  彼得
Yes, you can, Peter.
我为那份证词准备了几个月
I spent months on that testimony.
还游说委员会  我们全体员工...
I lobbied the commission. My entire office...
我相信你一定做得很好
I'm sure you've done splendid work,
不幸的是  这事成不了
but unfortunately it can't come to fruition.
-为什么  -这就是政治
- Why? - Politics.
有些势力是你我无力抗衡的
There's forces bigger than either of us at play here.
那可是12000人的饭碗啊
It's 12,000 jobs.
我明白  真令人遗憾
I know. It's a shame.
我就是保住了那家造船厂才得以当选
Keeping that shipyard open is what got me elected.
那些人是我的朋友
Those people are my friends.
我来不是和你争这个的  彼得
I'm not here to debate this, Peter.
工厂必须关闭
The base will close.
唯一的问题是
The only question is,
你选择长痛还是短痛
will you make it a swift death or a painful one?
不行  我不能坐视不管
No way. I won't sit on my hands.
这对你很难  我表示同情
I sympathize that this is gonna be difficult for you.
现在我说不出
And I don't know how yet,
但将来我会弥补你的  彼得
but I will make it up to you, Peter.
对于你  我是个强大的朋友
I'm a powerful friend to have right now,
或许是你唯一的朋友
perhaps your only friend,
别违抗我
so don't defy me.
家庭之爱
Love of family.
大多数政客终生都被这句口号所束缚
Most politicians are permanently chained to that slogan...
"家庭价值"
family values.
要是你和妓女厮混  又被我发现
But when you cozy up to hookers and I find out,
你就得为这份虚伪付出代价
I will make that hypocrisy hurt.
收到我送你的礼物了吗
Did you get the present I sent you?
称不上是礼物吧
You wouldn't really call it a present.
更像是个温柔的提醒吧
Well, more of a gentle reminder, maybe.
不怎么温柔  挺粗暴的
Mm, more heavy-handed than gentle,
真没想到啊
which surprised me.
这不是你的风格  弗兰西斯
It's not really your style, Francis.
是的  我收到了
But, yes. I got it.
我喜欢这件
I like that one.
我也是
I do too.
但第一件更好
But the first one's better.
是吗
You think?
明天有什么事吗
Something special tomorrow?
亚当・嘉乐威要从纽约过来
Adam Galloway's coming down from New York.
什么事
What for?
我需要他的一些照片
Because I need some of his photographs
下个月无声拍卖会上要用
for the silent auction at the gala next month.
跟雷米谈过了吗
You speak to Remy yet?
还没有
I haven't.
如果想显得诱惑些  穿黑色那件
If you want to look inviting, wear the black one.
你好
Hello.
好的  很好  谢谢
Oh. Okay. Great. Thanks.
亚当
Adam?
世界瞬息万变
How is it the world keeps spinning
你却总能走在前面
and you manage to stay ahead of it?
大卫也同意了
David's on board with this?
这就是他的主意
It was his idea.
那他为什么没来
Then why isn't he here?
这事还没定下前  我们得小心
Well, we have to be careful until it's a done deal.
我说不好  弗兰克
I don't know, Frank.
想想看  泰瑞
Think about it, Terry.
你会成为美国国会首位
You could become the first African-American majority leader
非裔多数党领袖
in the United States congress.
我们一起创造历史吧
Let's make some history.
你才不在乎什么历史呢
You don't care about history.
你找我是因为我能拉到选票
You just wanted me because I can round up the votes.
我是需要选票  但历史我也是在乎的
I need the votes, and I do care about history,
但最重要的是  泰瑞
but most importantly, Terry,
你有领袖风范
you know how to lead.
你成为黑人党团领袖是不无原因的
You're the head of the black caucus for a reason.
那么大卫当议长  我当多数党领袖
So David becomes speaker, I become majority leader...
我仍然做我的党鞭
and I stay on as whip.
你为什么不自己当多数党领袖
Why don't you want majority leader for yourself?
我对现状很满意
I'm satisfied where I am.
或许等哪天  你做了议长
Maybe one day, when you become speaker,
会提拔一下我
you'll bump me up.
这种事一旦决定就没有回头路了
This is the sort of thing that there's no turning back.
我还能给你锦上添个花
I can throw a cherry on top.
麦喀顿基地不关闭
McCudden stays open.
怎么做
How?
着你不会想知道
You don't want to know how.
你只需要头条新闻
You just want the headline
你保住了选区内的三千份工作
when you keep 3,000 jobs in your district.
-12张选票  -12张选票
- 12 votes? - 12 votes.
我能给你搞定10张  或许11张
I can get you 10, probably 11.
和这样的人合作真令人振奋
It's so refreshing to work with someone
对到手的礼物不吹毛求疵
who will throw a saddle on a gift horse
而能让它物尽其用
rather than look it in the mouth.
这张很不错
That's nice.
我是在阿姆拉维蒂外的一个小镇上看到她的
I found her in a village outside Amravati.
她叫蒂阿拉
Her name was Tiala.
拍下这张照片后三周她就去世了
She died three weeks after I took that picture.
这太可怕了
Oh, that's awful.
如果你喜欢  就都给你
You can have them all if you like.
我喜欢你短发的样子
I love your hair short.
今晚有安排吗
Do you have plans tonight?
没有
No.
弗兰克会在家等你吗
Is Frank expecting you home?
我想他应该会很晚到家
I'm sure he'll be home late.
和我一起吃晚餐
Get dinner with me.
你几点的火车
What time is your train?
我没订返程票
I don't book round-trip tickets.
我还要好一会儿才能下班
It's going to be a while before I can leave.
几点结束
What time will you be done?
大概八点左右
Probably around 8:00.
我去选个地方
I'll pick a place,
选好之后跟你说
let you know.
大卫
Ah. David.
还好吗  乔
How are you, Joe?
我站在你这边  我们好好干
I'm behind you. Let's do this.
干什么
Do what?
保持谨慎
Keep your cards close.
我喜欢
I like that.
你好  这是1214号房间
Hi. Yeah. This is room 1214.
麻烦来一瓶温巴赫
I'd like a bottle of the Weinbach, please.
是的
Yeah.
还是来两瓶吧
Actually, could you make that two bottles?
谢谢
Thank you.
坐吧  你这样我紧张
Sit down. You're making me nervous.
-你还抽烟吗  -偶尔还抽
- You still smoke? - From time to time, yes.
我戒了  这些都是幻觉
I quit. These are an illusion.
来一根
You want?
好啊
Sure.
怎么了
What?
现在不行
Not now.
好吧
Okay.
我得走了
I should go.
-我只是  我以为  -我知道
- I just... it seemed... - I know.
我们不能再这样了
We can't start this again.
我结束掉的事不会再做
When I end something, I end it.
那你大老远的把我从纽约叫来干什么
So why'd you have me come all the way down from New York?
我错了
It was a mistake.
对不起  亚当
I'm sorry, Adam.
我不应该掺杂私情的
I should've kept it business.
我最不喜欢的就是你这点
Side of you I like the least.
没有错可言  克莱尔
There are no mistakes, Claire.
晚上好
Hello.
再来点酒
More wine?
你今天过得怎么样
How was your day?
-很好  -亚当也好吗
- Good. - Adam well?
是的
He is.
我们刚吃过晚饭
We just had dinner.
回家路上我给雷米发邮件了
I e-mailed Remy on the way home.
我告诉他钱我不要了
I told him I'm not taking the money.
谢谢
Thank you.
我很感激  这对你并不容易
I appreciate that this was not easy.
难才对我们胃口  不是吗
Well, we don't like easy, do we?
事实证明  确实如此
Oh, the evidence would suggest it.
周三晚上可以邀霍博恩夫妇来吃饭吗
Is it all right if the holburns come over for dinner Wednesday night?
我想让费莉希蒂在拍卖会上竞拍
I want Felicity to buy some tables for the gala.
好的  没问题
Yeah, of course.
得有国会议员和参议员出席
I'm going to need congressmen and senators there.
-你得找人帮忙  -没问题
- You need to call in favors. - Done.
不是一两个  要很多
Not a few, a lot.
我明天一早就打电话
I'll start making calls in the morning.
亚当捐了十张照片
Adam donated ten photographs.
他真大方
That was generous of him.
他住在文华酒店
He's staying at the mandarin.
你呢
And you?
在这儿
Here.
但是试验场的重要性
But the proving grounds' importance
远超出其地理位置的战略价值
stems far beyond it's strategic geographic value.
APG研发的军用材料
A.P.G.'s research and development of military materiel
对于我国的反恐工作至关重要
is central to our nation's counter-terrorism efforts.
基地研究试验预防性药物
The base houses research laboratories for preventative medicine
并且为军事人员提供多种训练场地
as well as a wide variety of training grounds for military personnel.
APG同时还促进就业
A.P.G. Is also a job creator.
每年提供4亿美元的薪酬
It provides 400 million dollars in payroll annually,
还有将近5亿美元的订单
and nearly half a billion dollars in contracts.
感谢能有机会在各位面前作证
Thank you for the opportunity to testify before you today.
有人想提问马里兰州的议员吗
Any questions for the congresswoman from Maryland?
没有
No.
赞成将阿伯丁试验场
Those in favor of removing the aberdeen proving ground
从关闭名单移除的
from the list of closures?
赞成
Aye.
记录并移除
So noted and removed.
接下来是费城海军造船厂
Okay, we'll next consider the Philadelphia naval shipyard.
宾州一选区的国会议员
Would the congressman from Pennsylvania's first district
有什么证词吗
like to offer testimony?
没有证词
I have no testimony to offer.
是的  但是我们将做的改变
Yeah, but the difference that we're gonna make...
泰瑞  我稍后打给你
Uh, Terry, let me call you right back.
泰瑞・乌麦克
Terry Womack?
或许吧
Possibly.
已经有三个黑人党团成员来找我说
I've had three members of the Black Caucus tell me
他们支持我竞争议长一职
they're backing my play for the speakership.
真有意思
Interesting.
依我看是你在散布一些谣言
I have a sense you've been disseminating some misinformation.
不  我看是你听闻不实  大卫
No. I'm afraid it's you who are misinformed, David.
支持你的不止三人  而是十人
You don't have three members backing you. You have ten.
我说得很清楚  我不想参与进来
I made it very clear I didn't want any part of this.
没错  你是说得很清楚
Yes, you made it crystal clear.
那你为什么要那么说
Then why are you telling people?
因为这个他们并不知道
Because they don't know you made it crystal clear.
我必须得去告诉鲍勃
I have to go to Bob with this.
他会觉得你策划了一场政变
He'll think you organized a coup,
半路退缩了  拿我当替罪羊
got cold feet, and are making me the scapegoat.
大卫  如果我现在拿起电话
David, if I pick up this phone right now
把这件事透露出去
and leak this story,
鲍勃就只能抛弃你
Bob will have no choice but to drop you,
即使他真的相信了你的话
even if he believes your version of events.
要不要坐下
You wanna take a seat?
弗莱迪烧烤餐馆
-弗莱迪  -什么事  弗兰克
- Uh, Freddy? - Yeah, Frank?
就给我来半份吧  晚上有晚宴
You better make it a half order. I got a big dinner tonight.
没问题
Sure thing.
生菜色拉
Slaw?
-老样子  -好咧
- Always. - You got it.
来了
Here you go.
最近怎么样
So, what's the latest?
你懂的  弗兰克  还是老样子
Oh, you know, Frank. Same old shit.
上周末差点没命了
Almost got killed last weekend.
-在这里  -不是
- Here? - No.
去弗吉尼亚展览会的路上
State fair down in Virginia.
我和弟弟开着改装车去那里
Me and my brother hauling this smoker down there,
有辆该死的小货车车顶绑着冰箱
and this fucking minivan had a fridge strapped on top.
冰箱绑在货车顶  弗兰克
A fridge strapped on top of a minivan, Frank.
太蠢了
That's stupid.
冰箱的绳结松了
Well, that fridge slipped loose.
轰隆一声砸在我们面前
Boom! Right in front of us.
我只能急左转  差点碰上
I had to swerve to the left. Barely missed it.
但这下我的车就摆尾行驶了
But now that smoker is fishtailing,
差点撞上邻车道的掀背车
almost hit a hatchback in the next lane.
再急右转  又差点出事
Swerved to the right. Barely missed that too.
-天哪  -老兄  是真的
- Jesus. - Oh, man, it was real.
所以上帝才会给我们反射弧
But, you know, that's why God gave us reflexes.
好躲开从天而降的冰箱
So we can move the fuck out of the way when a fridge come out of nowhere.
-肋排怎么样  -你知道的
- How them ribs? - You know how they are.
-我喜欢听你说  -完美  弗莱迪
- You know I like to hear it. - Perfection, Freddy.
无可挑剔
Perfection.
-你接着吃吧  弗兰克  -谢谢  弗莱迪
- You go on ahead, Frank. - Thank you, Freddy.
真是意外啊
Well, this is a surprise.
-你一般发短信  -你在哪
- You usually text. - Where are you?
逆道而行
On the other side of the tracks
试图寻找人生的意义
trying to find the meaning of life.
你为我找到什么了吗
Did you find anything for me?
你指有报导价值的事
You mean anything newsworthy?
其实我不是打来纠缠你的
Uh, I actually didn't call to badger you.
你就是  不过这也是你的魅力
Yes, you did, but that's part of your charm.
不是
No.
我想告诉你我刚被提升为
I wanted to tell you that I've been promoted to
驻白宫记者
White House correspondent.
我得随记者团到处走  参加通气会
I'll have to travel with the press corps, be at briefings,
但我可以应付得来
but I can work around all that.
如果你需要我  我还会一如既往
If you need me. It won't change anything.
正相反
Oh, on the contrary.
这改变了一切
This changes everything.
不  我很变通的
No. I can be flexible.
我对变通的人没兴趣
I'm not interested in someone who's flexible,
我只对有空的人感兴趣
I'm interested in someone who's available.
你是说我该拒绝
So you think I should turn it down?
这完全取决于你
That's entirely up to you.
好吧  还没正式确定
Well, I mean, it's not official yet.
-我可以  -我得挂了
- I could... - Oh, look, I've got to go,
等你又有空了  再打给我
but call me, you know, if you find yourself available again.
弗莱迪认为如果冰箱从小货车上掉下来
You see, Freddy believes that if a fridge falls off a minivan,
你得赶快避开
you better swerve out of its way.
我却认为冰箱该给我让道
I believe it's the fridge's job to swerve out of mine.
简宁
Hey, Janine...
走开  佐伊  我现在没心情和你聊
Keep walking, Zoe. I really don't want to talk to you right now.
又不是我去找他的
It's not like I asked him for it.
-他把我叫进办公室  -拜托
- He just called me into his office, and... - Oh, please.
自从你含着棒棒糖蹦蹦来这儿工作
You've been gunning for my job since the day you bounced in here
就一直觊觎我的职位
with a lollipop in your mouth.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
我会从中西部给你寄瓶香槟
I'll send you a bottle of champagne from the Middle West,
不知道那是什么鬼地方
wherever the fuck that is.
我不会接受的  你不用走
I'm gonna turn it down. You don't have to leave.
你这是有意跟我显摆吗
Are you trying to rub this in or something?
请相信我  你该待在白宫
Please believe me. You should be in the White House.
我不想去  从来都不
I don't want it. I never did.
我希望我们能一起去见汤姆
I was hoping we could go see Tom together.
告诉他我们都
I want him to know that we both...
给我滚开
Get the fuck out of my face.
我在请求你  真心的
I'm asking. For real.
我不想要那份工作
I don't want the job.
那你比我想的还蠢
Then you're an even bigger idiot than I thought you were.
滚开  别逼我动手
Go. Before I get violent.
彼得
Peter?
有人吗
Hello?
但白令海的力量猛烈而难以捉摸
But the Bering Sea is a violent and unpredictable force.
我叫克里斯蒂娜
Hi. Uh, my name is Christina.
-你们爸爸的同事  -他不在
- I work with your dad. - He's not here.
-他去哪了  -我不知道
- Where'd he go? - I don't know.
他说很快就回来
He said he'd be back in a little while.
什么时候说的
Uh, when was that?
把我们从学校接回来的时候
When he dropped us home from school.
他没带手机
He left his phone here.
你是爸爸的女朋友吗
Are you dad's girlfriend?
不  我
No. No. I, uh...
我不过是你们爸爸的下属
I just... I... I work for your dad.
那你为什么会有他公寓的钥匙
Then why do you have the keys to his apartment?
你能做点果酱馅饼吗
Will you make us pop-tarts?
18米的巨浪袭击阿留申群岛
An enormous 60-foot rogue wave struck the Aleutian...
真是丰盛可口  克莱尔
It was just sublime, Claire.
-谢谢  -我大概这个礼拜都不用进食了
- Thank you. - I don't think I'll eat for a week.
连甜点也不吃了吗
Does that mean no room for dessert?
真想吃  不过算了
I'd love to, but, uh, none for me.
那我们下楼去
Why don't you and I head downstairs
来点白兰地雪茄什么的
for a little Brandy and some cigars?
古巴雪茄吗
Cubans?
你觉得我会私藏违禁物品吗
You don't think I smoke anything legal, do you?
1962年2月7日  美国前总统肯尼迪对古巴实施禁运
-甜点要吗  -不  谢谢
- Dessert for you? - No. No, thanks.
不过我想再来点夏敦埃
But I will take a refill of this Chardonnay, though.
没问题
Of course.
这瓶快喝完了  我去再去拿一瓶
Oh, this is almost out. I'll grab another.
我也讨厌这样  突然就上来股劲
I hate how they just hit you like that with no warning.
你也盗汗吗
You get night sweats too?
我
I, uh...
我对这个没什么经验
This is very new to me.
弗兰克知道吗
Does Frank know?
我还没  我们  不
I haven't... we haven't... no.
对不起  我们没必要谈这个的
I'm sorry. We don't have to talk about this.
不  没关系  只是
No. It's fine. I'm just, uh...
没事  我感觉好多了
It's fine. I feel better now.
-我可以再来一点吗  -当然
- Could I have a little bit more? - Sure.
够了就说
Just say when.
今晚查尔斯开车  所以
Charles is driving tonight, so...
够了
And when.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
你邀我来的时候提到了净水计划
So, you mentioned, when you invited me, the C.W.I.
说是举办了活动庆祝新项目的开启
You're having a gala and launching some new...
对  是这样的
Yes, that's right.
我们刚请来一位非常棒的女士
We just brought on this brilliant young woman
她会帮我们开拓海外项目
who's going to help us expand our efforts overseas.
-这样我们  -克莱尔
- So we'll... - Claire, I will
不必多说了
save you the trouble.
查尔斯和我非常乐意出力
Charles and I would be delighted to contribute.
你真是太慷慨了  费莉希蒂
Well, that's very generous of you, Felicity.
你还好心
Well, you were such a darling,
帮我们弄到了杰弗逊舞会的入场券呢
getting us tickets to the Jefferson Ball.
-举手之劳  -不  不止这样
- Oh, that was nothing. - It wasn't nothing.
这是
It was...
这座城市里的人  不会费心善待他人
People in this town don't go out of their way to be nice to each other.
查尔斯和我在这儿待了14年
Fourteen years Charles and I have been here, and...
总之
Anyway, um,
我很高兴能交到一位朋友
I'm grateful to have a friend.
你需要多少钱
How much do you need?
克里斯蒂娜  你怎么会在这里
Christina, what the fuck are you doing here?
小声点  他们睡了
Shh. They're sleeping.
彼得
Peter.
-爸爸好  -孩子们
- Hey, dad. - Hey, kiddo.
带你弟弟下楼好吗
Would you take your brother downstairs?
-我一会儿就来  -嗯  爸爸再见
- I'll be there in a second. - Okay. Bye, dad.
-再见  -为什么再见  他们要去哪
- Bye. - Bye? Where they going?
去他们奶奶那儿
I'm taking them to their grandmother's.
我联系上了玛德琳  跟她说...
I was able to get a hold of Madeleine, and I told her...
别跟我说你告诉她了
Oh, fuck. You didn't tell her?
没  不过我应该说的
No, I didn't. But I should have.
我说你要因公出差
I told her that you had to travel for work,
这是我最后一次为你说谎了
which is the last time I ever lie for you.
听着
Look...
究竟怎么回事  彼得
what happened, Peter?
听证会的事我很抱歉
I'm... I'm sorry about the Brack hearing.
-我  -去他妈的听证会
- I was... - Fuck the Brack hearing.
想想你的孩子
What about your kids?
我把他们送过去  我们就算完了
After I drop them off, I'm done.
我不再是你的女友  也不为你工作
I am no longer your girlfriend. I no longer work for you.
不  等等  克里斯蒂娜
No... hey, Christina...
我不想听  彼得
I don't want to hear it, Peter.
这次别想找借口
There's no excuse this time.
我很忙  弗兰克
I don't have much time, Frank.
我会长话短说
I'll make it short.
-关于总统吗  -不  关于议长
- The President? - No. The speakership.
大卫有所动作
David's making a play.
-什么  -他找我支持他
- What? - He came to me for support.
我一开始本想马上告诉你
My first thought was to tell you right away,
不过转念一想  算了
but then my second thought was to ignore my first thought,
我们票数够了  鲍勃
because we have the votes, Bob.
要是党内有情况  我不可能不知道
If there had been a party revolt, I would've known about it.
不需要全党反对  13人足以
We don't need the whole party to revolt. We need 13...
13个民主党  加上对立党派
13 Democrats, plus the other side of the aisle.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
最近这么问的人挺多
People have been asking me that a lot lately.
我有点想回答"是的"
I'm inclined to start saying yes.
那13个是谁
Who are they... the 13?
大卫加我就是两个  泰瑞・乌麦克
David and I are two, Terry Womack,
黑人党团10个人  一共13个
and ten members of the black caucus make another 11.
总统的意思吗
Is the President behind this?
不  他完全不知道
No. He doesn't have a clue.
大卫策划的  我是跑腿的
This was David's plan executed by me.
你还是有生路的  鲍勃
But there is an out for you, Bob.
乌麦克哪边倒全听我的
I can sway Womack either way
前提是你让他成为下任多数党领袖
as long as you make him the next majority leader.
还有
And...
-教育法案  -这下你跟上我的思路了
- The education bill. - Now we're on the same page.
你知道我不能那么做
I can't do that. You know I can't.
你是议长  鲍勃  你做什么都行
You're the speaker, Bob. You can do anything you'd like.
我得说
And I have to say,
任命首位非裔美国人做多数党领袖
appointing the first African-American majority leader...
这可是宝贵的功绩啊
why, that isn't a bad legacy to have.
抱歉  我改主意了
I'm sorry. I changed my mind.
我考虑过了
I thought about it, and...
我给过你两天时间考虑了
Thinking about it was what those two days were for.
然后我又好好想了一下  我意识到
And then I thought about it some more, and I realized I...
上帝啊  你太不可理喻了
Jesus Christ, you're fucking unbelievable.
汤姆  我非常感激你给我机会  但...
Look, Tom, I appreciate the fact that you took a chance on me, but...
不  你才不会呢
No, I don't think you do.
你根本不懂感激
I don't think you appreciate anything.
你就是个忘恩负义  自以为是的小
I think you're an ungrateful, self-entitled little c...
小什么
Little what?
小什么  汤姆  说出来
Little what, Tom? Say it.
贱人  你是个贱人
Cunt. You're a cunt.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
你要是敢
Don't you dare...
你都不知道我在打什么
You don't even know what I'm typing.
-出去  佐伊  -等等  我快好了
- Get out, Zoe. - Just a second. I'm almost done.
出去  你被炒了
Get out. You're fired.
随你怎么说吧  汤姆
Whatever you have to tell yourself, Tom.
出去
Get out!
我应该按"发送"吗
So should I press "Send"?
我想是吧
I think I should.
随你怎么喊我
Call me whatever you want,
但别忘了  如今
but you should remember, these days,
信息的传播速度可非常快
when you're talking to one person, you're talking to a thousand.
华盛顿先驱报
你就说你想花更多时间
Well, you'll say you wanted to spend more time
专注于自己的选区
focusing on your home district.
乌麦克是接替你职位的不二人选
You'll say Womack is the right man to fill your shoes.
不要兴风作浪  不要接受采访
You won't make waves. You won't do interviews.
把苦咽下去  维护团队利益
You'll suck it up and be a team player.
这是弗兰克的主意
This was Frank's idea.
我就说他会把这都赖我头上
I told you he was gonna try to blame me on it.
到处去问问  和乌麦克谈谈
Ask around. Talk to Womack.
我谈过了  他说是你找他的
I did. He said you came to him.
他在撒谎  鲍勃  我绝不会...
He's fucking lying, Bob! I would never...
闭嘴  大卫
Shut up, David.
你知道我们宣布的时候该怎么做吗
Do you understand how you're to behave when we make the announcement?
如果我不合作呢
And if I don't play along?
那么民主党竞选委员会将在下届竞选中
Then the D-triple-C will pour everything it's got
倾尽所有支持你的主要对手
into your primary opponent's campaign next cycle.
我们会把你踢出局
We'll cleave you from the herd
看着你自生自灭
and watch you die in the wilderness.
马上做决定  大卫
Tell us now, David.
如你所愿  罗伯特
If you think it's best, Robert.
想想看  他本可以做头狼的
And just think, he could have been a wolf.
这下你有空了
You made yourself available.
我辞职了
I quit.
去那个鬼地方
Fuck that place.
就像监牢  现在我自由了
It was a prison. I'm free now.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你在哪里
Where are you?
-车里  -我也是
- In a car. - So am I.
你要去哪里
Where you headed?
-回家  -我也是
- Home. - So am I.
回你家还是我家
To your home or mine?
这算邀请吗
Is that an invitation?
你说算就算
It's whatever you want it to be.
-你好像喝醉了  -是的
- You sound tipsy. - I am.
我刚喝了两小时的长岛冰茶
I just spent the last two hours drinking Long Island Iced Teas.
你家在哪里
What's your address?
你父母知道你住这种地方吗
Do your parents know you live like this?
不  他们没来过
No. They haven't visited.
有人照顾你吗
Are you cared for?
什么意思
How do you mean?
有男人照顾你吗
Do you have a man who cares for you?
-年长的男人  -没有
- An older man. - No.
但你以前和老男人处过
But you've been with older men before?
是的
Yes.
那你该知道他们会伤害你
Then you know they hurt you,
在那之后
and after they hurt you,
就会遗弃你
they discard you.
你伤不了我
You can't hurt me.
把高跟鞋脱了
Take your heels off.
■
每年美国国会议员们会提交很多提案  但只有少数能进入立法程序
国会里的议员影响力天差地别  而议长能做最终的定夺
本集开篇部分  卫生间对话提到的platform特指一个党的核心思想
美国四年一次的党全国代表大会  主要是提名选举本党总统候选人
同时也通过一个包含中心思想的platform  相当于我国的党章
民主党重视教育  所以教育改革应该是民主党章程的内容之一
■
本集还提到黑人党团
国会议员会根据自己的背景组成小团体  在投票的时候一起行动
如黑人党团  拉丁裔党团等等
佐伊与卢卡斯对话中提到的big dinner party
是指一年一度的"The White House correspondents dinner"
驻白宫记者晚宴  一般在四五月份  由驻白宫记者协会主办
总统会参加  并在会上讲话  主要是讲笑话
还会请一位嘉宾  一般是比较知名的脱口秀主持人  也要讲笑话
晚宴每年都会吸引很多注意
翻译  天意
翻译  小饭
翻译  小蟹
翻译  某羽
翻译  音司忐忑
翻译  风吹日落
翻译  痒痒
翻译  ~某人_
翻译  u油
翻译   sakura
时间轴  chance-coco
顾问  老杜
后期  饿得慌
校对  草草
总监  草草
纸牌屋
第一季  第四集
人人影视倾情奉献